PREPROCESSING
1) remove preamble
   e.g. "80032 3/11/2011 3/13/2011"

2) remove boilerplate text at the end of the article
   e.g. "For more information..."

3) convert uppercase headlines to titlecase
   e.g.    "HIBBETT ANNOUNCES INITIAL AFFECT OF HURRICANE KATRINA"
   becomes "Hibbett Announces Initial Affect Of Hurricane Katrina"

4) remove headline if specified



POSTPROCESSING
1) if the market of a ticker was recognized as an organization, discard it
   e.g.     (<ORGANIZATION>Nasdaq</ORGANIZATION>: C)
   becomes  (Nasdaq: C)

2) if the surface of an organization in the headline contains an action, split it on the action and take the first part
   e.g.     <ORGANIZATION>Shaw Issues a Statement</ORGANIZATION>
   becomes  <ORGANIZATION>Shaw</ORGANIZATION> Issues a Statement

3) if the surface of an organization in the headline contains an extraneous noun, split it on the noun and take the first part
   e.g.     <ORGANIZATION>Shaw Update:</ORGANIZATION>
   becomes  <ORGANIZATION>Shaw</ORGANIZATION> Update:

4) if a date with pattern "MM/DD/YY" was not recognized, add it
   e.g.     1/13/06
   becomes  <DATE>1/13/06</DATE>

5) if a date with pattern "YYYY-MM-DD" was not recognized, add it
   e.g.    2016-01-01
   becomes <DATE>2016-01-01</DATE>

6) if a time with pattern "HH:MM:SS" was not recognized, add it
   e.g.    22:00:05
   becomes <TIME>22:00:05</TIME>

7) if an organization is followed by a ticker, merge the two
   e.g.     <ORGANIZATION>Entergy Corporation</ORGANIZATION> <ORGANIZATION>(NYSE: ETR)</ORGANIZATION>
   becomes  <ORGANIZATION>Entergy Corporation (NYSE: ETR)</ORGANIZATION>

8) if a time is followed by "UTC", merge the two
   e.g.    <TIME>20:36:14</TIME> UTC
   becomes <TIME>20:36:14 UTC</TIME>

9) if a location is followed by another location that represents its US State, merge the two
   e.g.    <LOCATION>BATON ROUGE</LOCATION>, <LOCATION>La.</LOCATION>
   becomes <LOCATION>BATON ROUGE, La.</LOCATION>

10) if a person is preceded by a personal title, merge the two
   e.g.    Mr <PERSON>Bernhard</PERSON>
   becomes <PERSON>Mr Bernhard</PERSON>
